Nasu Oyaji Curry
The Kobe trip ended safely.
And summer break
was nearing its end.
Casual clothes.
Chinatown. Sun parasol and pizza.
The aquarium...
The scent of Senpai's shampoo...
Holding hands, and having fun.
More and more, it's becoming not enough...
Yoi! Yoi!
Yoi!
The rice! The rice!
Oh!
The rice...
Oh, man...
It's surprisingly slow today.
Maybe I should ask Asami to
bring her college friends over.
I think Sis would be pissed.
Yep, I know.
Oh, how about the kids
at your school, Yoi?
You know! That boy...
The curry fanatic!
Oh, him.
I'm the curry fanatic!
Business sure is slow.
I haven't seen Senpai
since the Kobe trip.
I've been busy with this and that...
If I'd known this would happen,
I would have kept my schedule
open a little more...
Welcome...
Yo.
Senpai?!
What brought this on?
Just came by to eat curry.
Can I sit anywhere?
Oh, please, go ahead.
So, I'd like one special. Large.
Oh, he really did just
come here for curry.
Uh, and for my drink...
iced coffee.
Welcome.
Oh!
Hello.
Oji-kun.
I was passing by, so I figured
I'd stop by for dinner.
Yeah, come in and eat.
Hello.
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Thanks for the grub.
Yoi, can you handle the register?
Oh, yeah.
One moment, please.
Um, one large special.
And the drink was...
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Thank you for coming!
It was real good as always.
It's been a while since I've
had something nourishing.
I'm glad to hear that.
You keep eating from
the convenience store...
Don't you ever go back
to your parents' house to eat?
What? No way. It's a pain.
Besides, don't you ever get the
urge to eat junk food for dinner?
Like burgers and takoyaki.
Oh, takoyaki... That's true.
I'd like to eat a whole bunch for dinner.
I wonder how many I could eat.
What are you imagining right now?
Maybe ten?
Burgers are good, too.
Oh... a takoyaki burger...
Then, wanna have a takoyaki party
date sometime?
At my place.
His place?
Hey, don't freeze up on me now.
I-Is that what this was leading to?!
I thought we were just making
small talk after the curry!
Y'know...
Can't you stop, think, and realize
that I came to see you?
For the record, I am inviting you over.
Oh... Um... I-If...
If my schedule frees up,
I'll think about it.
Hey, come on. Let's be
a little more proactive here.
But I have work and other things...
Nobara-chan
Nobara-chan!
Did you finish your homework?!
Not yet.
Oh, good! Me neither!
Do you think Yoi-chan got it done?
The Prince? I'm sure she did.
That's right! Yoi-chan-sama would!
By the way, about Yoi-chan.
Don't you think she seemed like
she was getting along with Senpai
real well when we were in Kobe?
Oh, I know, right?
She just might be meeting
up with Senpai as we speak...
Thank you very much!
Oh, hey!
Yo!
Are things with the Prince going well?
You're such a pain.
Oh, but...
I was wondering whatever
happened to that dude.
Y'know, the part-timer?
The handsome guy.
Oh, beats me.
I think he still works there?
Don't know, though.
Uh-huh...
What?
Well, it's just...
That guy seemed like he had
his eyes on the Prince.
Like they had some real
chemistry, or something.
Well, I might just be
overthinking it, but...
Kuwa...
Hmm?
Don't drop weird hints at me, man.
My bad. My bad.
Don't take it seriously.
First of all, there's no way anything
like that would happen with Yoi-chan.
Well, true.
But what if something were to...
Kuwa! Why, you!
My bad, my bad! I'm kiddin'! I'm kiddin'!
Why ya little... Take that! And that!
Hey, stop that!
At my place...
Yoi-chan, Yoi-chan, Yoi-chan-sensei!
Huh?
We solved the problem.
Huh? Oh, then you think you
could solve this next one?
For this problem, you apply this part of
the problem we just did, and...
If we're going to be at
his house alone together...
Are we going to kiss... and stuff?
Oh, yeah, yeah. That's it.
No, we're there to have takoyaki! Yep!
Sensei's weird today.
Yeah.
I can't picture it.
I wonder what it's like...
No!
Like I said, we're there
to have takoyaki...!
Besides, it's not like my schedule is
going to conveniently free up anyway.
Nasu Oyaji Curry
We apologize for the inconvenience,
but we will be temporarily closed today.
I got it!
Huh? What did you get?
A winning lottery ticket?
No! I got food poisoning!
Was it the meal set I had for lunch?
For now, I'm going to the hospital,
so close up the shop for me!
You two can take today off!
Make sure you lock the doors
and turn off the gas and lights!
I guess we'll close up shop
and go home for today.
Yeah.
My schedule... is freed up.
If my schedule frees up,
I'll think about it.
Since I was the one who said that, I
should be the one to contact him... right?
But if I do that...
Um.
Do you have some free time right now?
I'm sorry for putting you through this.
No worries. They put my dad on an
IV drip so he's all right now.
I did promise to help you pick
out a present for your sister.
I'm sorry.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
I'll meet with Senpai another time.
By the way, how old is
your younger sister?
She's in third grade.
Third grade, huh?
I wonder what she'd like.
What did you want at that age, Yoi-san?
Um... I was taking karate back then,
so something like a sports bottle.
Or a face towel.
That would make me really happy.
Oh, I know what you mean!
I was into soccer, too.
That sort of thing does make
you happy, like a sports bag.
Nice one.
Oh.
Do you want to check it out?
I'm sorry. I kept buying things for myself.
No, same.
We kind of got distracted, didn't we?
Let's just look it up on online.
Hair accessories
Cute stationary
Toys
Clothes
Play makeup
Watches
Elementary School Girl Present
Top 6 things to give to an elementary school girl
Clothes
Oh.
Thank you for coming!
Seems like it was just faster
to look it up, after all.
I'm sorry about that.
Well then, shall we?
Uh... Um!
Would you like to stop
by one more place?
Are you sure about this?
Paying for my treat...
It's the least I could do to say thanks.
But...
Thank you so much.
I didn't have anyone else
I could ask about this,
so you really helped me out.
I've been wondering about
this for a while...
Don't you have a girlfriend
or something, Oji-kun?
N-No, not at all!
You seem like you'd be popular.
I-I'm not popular.
I go to an all-boys school, anyway.
Also...
I spend a lot of time playing sports,
so I'm not used to being around girls.
I'm never sure what to talk about, and...
Even in folk dancing, I couldn't bring
myself to take a girl's hand...
I...
I understand!
You can't look them in the eye, right?!
Yeah, yeah!
Also, I'd end up using
honorifics the whole time,
and since I'm not used to it, my
speech comes across really cold.
Right?
Yes!
We have lots in common, don't we?
So, do you like anyone?
No?
Huh, Takuto?!
Iguchi, Taoka!
Didn't you say you had work today?
What are you doing here?
Hey, are you a girl?!
And here I thought he was
walking with a really handsome guy!
Whoa, no kiddin'! Wow!
You look so cool!
Hey, that's rude, you two!
Oh, right, sorry.
Sorry.
Oh, no, don't worry about it.
I'm seriously sorry.
No, really, don't worry
about it. I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
About what happened back there.
My friends were being rude to you.
Oh...
No, really, it's okay.
I'm used to it. Besides...
I used to be self-conscious about it,
but now it doesn't bother me as much.
Was there something particular
that helped you with that?
The thing that helped me was...
For the first time ever,
someone treated me like a girl.
I'm sorry!
Honestly, what am I even saying?
Please forget what I said.
Yoi-san.
You have cream on your face.
Huh, oh...
Oh, on the other side.
Oh.
Right here.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
Didn't... something like
this happen before?
The lassi!
I'm sorry for doing that every time.
I do have someone I like.
Right in front of me.
I saw you as a girl right
from the start, Yoi-san.
Well, see you later.
What...
What?
What?!
That was the very first time I ever
thought someone was beautiful.
Huh? Did it shrink again?
177.9 cm.
My you're growing so quickly.
In one year, you've grown more than 10 cm.
You're lucky, Oji.
I wanna be tall, too.
Hey, it went that way!
Hey, over here, over here!
Hey, don't you think Oji's a hottie?
I know, right? He's really
standing out lately.
He had a cute face to begin with.
Don't you think he has
the best-looking face?
He doesn't really talk to girls.
But he seems like he has his act together.
I know, right?
Takuto, let's go home!
Sure.
Hey, did you see that
soccer match yesterday?
Hey there.
Can we walk home with you guys, too?
Day Duty
Hasegawa
Honda
Caution
What, seriously?
That was amazing, wasn't it?
Oh, which reminds me!
Aw, man, I wanted to talk about
stupid stuff like we usually do.
Hey.
I'm this way, so...
I'm that way, too.
Can I walk with you?
What should I talk about
at times like these?
Hey, hey.
Huh?
What do guys usually talk about?
Uh, um...
We talk about club activities,
manga, and stuff.
And sometimes videos.
Huh, what kind of videos?
Oh... Mainly soccer commentaries
and overseas reaction videos.
Oh, there's this one channel that's
all about Indian food stalls...
People making tons of fried rice,
or putting toppers on cakes...
There's just always something
amazing happening...
Uh-huh...
Th-This is so awkward...
Even his name, "Oji," makes
him sound like a prince!
Right?
So cool!
No matter how tall I grew
or how my appearance changed,
I was still the same guy inside, playing
soccer and hanging with the guys.
Oji, you should come hang
with us, too, next time.
Oh, I have club activities, so...
And yet, the reaction from those
around me gradually changed...
I'm sorry!
I'm not interested in having
a girlfriend at the moment.
People kept expecting more from
me, raising the bar higher.
What? Takuto, you're going
to an all-boys school?
Huh, yeah. It's close.
It was getting harder and
harder to be around girls.
Senchan_Curry-san uploaded another video.
Whenever I watch his videos,
it makes me crave curry.
Actually, wasn't the curry place
someone showed me near here?
I should go check it out.
That's good!
Wow, what is this place? It's so good!
I'm gonna come here again for sure.
Don't you think that guy's good-looking?
Hiring Part-timers
Job position: Floor staff
Job Description: Register, customer service, etc.
Contact:
Right? So cool.
A part-time job, huh...
You're late.
Sorry, my train was delayed.
I think I just stared in awe.
That server is super handsome,
too, don't you think?
I know, right? He's super hot.
A man? That can't be.
Her arms and legs are slightly
longer than most women's.
The soft curve of the back of her neck.
The delicate fingers.
The precision of her movements.
I honestly thought she
was a beautiful person.
It was only a while later that I
realized it was "love at first sight."
What?
I do have someone I like.
Right in front of me.
Does that mean...
He...
likes me?
Another Prince
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis